Guide to the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust Records, 1975-2021 CTC.2000.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Marketing, 1975-1999; VIII.
  - Production marketing files, 1989-1999; 7.
    - Miss Saigon arts groups packages, 1996-1997 (Box 311, Folder 7-8)
    - Miss Saigon Bill Miller, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 1-2)
    - Miss Saigon bills and settlement, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 3)
    - Miss Saigon biographies, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 4)
    - Miss Saigon booking advisories, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - Miss Saigon casting, May 1997 (Box 312, Folder 6)
    - Miss Saigon Civic Light Opera, 1996-1997 (Box 312, Folder 7)
    - Miss Saigon Civic Light Opera advance sales reports, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 8)
    - Miss Saigon Charlotte media junket, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 9)
    - Miss Saigon contract, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 10)
    - Miss Saigon corporation discounts, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 11)
    - Miss Saigon Evening in Saigon gala, 1996-1997 (Box 312, Folder 12-13)
    - Miss Saigon expenses, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 14)
    - Miss Saigon From Saigon with Love Pittsburgh AIDS Task Force benefit, 1997 (Box 312, Folder 15)
    - Miss Saigon general information, 1996-1997 (Box 313, Folder 1-4)
    - Miss Saigon groups sales, 1997 (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Miss Saigon Heinz History Center promotion, 1997 (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - Miss Saigon house capacity, April 1997 (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - Miss Saigon house seats, 1996-1997 (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - Miss Saigon insertion orders, 1997 (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - Miss Saigon Kaufmann's promotion, 1997 (Box 313, Folder 10-12)
    - Miss Saigon KQV, 1997 (Box 313, Folder 13)
    - Miss Saigon limited view seat exchange, 1996-1997 (Box 313, Folder 14)
    - Miss Saigon limited view seat mailer, 1996-1997 (Box 313, Folder 15)
    - Miss Saigon live remote, April 1997 (Box 313, Folder 16)
    - Miss Saigon logos (Box 313, Folder 17)
    - Miss Saigon marketing, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Miss Saigon Maya Lin, 1996 (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - Miss Saigon media interviews, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Miss Saigon media seat requests, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Miss Saigon memos, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Miss Saigon news releases, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Miss Saigon newspaper clippings, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - Miss Saigon original file, 1994-1997 (Box 314, Folder 8)
    - Miss Saigon original invoices, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 9)
    - Miss Saigon outdoor advertising (Box 314, Folder 10)
    - Miss Saigon phase I mail order group and phone on-sale, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 11-12)
    - Miss Saigon phase II phone on-sale and advertising, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 13-14)
    - Miss Saigon phase III maintenance, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 15)
    - Miss Saigon phase IV box office on sale, 1997 (Box 314, Folder 16)
    - Miss Saigon phase V budget corrections, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Miss Saigon phase V insertions orders, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - Miss Saigon phase V July and August, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - Miss Saigon phase V through August 3, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - Miss Saigon phase V through August 10, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - Miss Saigon phase V through August 17, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - Miss Saigon phase V through August 24, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 7)
    - Miss Saigon phase V through August 31, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 8)
    - Miss Saigon phase V through September 7, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 9)
    - Miss Saigon phone sale, March 1997 (Box 315, Folder 10)
    - Miss Saigon pins (Box 315, Folder 11)
    - Miss Saigon program ads, 1995-1997 (Box 315, Folder 12)
    - Miss Saigon promotion materials, 1995-1997 (Box 315, Folder 13)
    - Miss Saigon promotion work plan, July 1997 (Box 315, Folder 14)
    - Miss Saigon proposals from radio stations, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 15)
    - Miss Saigon proposals from television stations, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 16)
    - Miss Saigon proposals received, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 17)
    - Miss Saigon receipts, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 18)
    - Miss Saigon revisited, 1997 (Box 315, Folder 19)
    - Miss Saigon rules, June 1997 (Box 315, Folder 20)
    - Miss Saigon sample promotional items, July 1996 (Box 315, Folder 21)
    - Miss Saigon schedules and time lines, March 1996 (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - Miss Saigon settlement, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 2)
    - Miss Saigon signed performance for the hearing impaired, September 1997 (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - Miss Saigon Sizzling Summer, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - Miss Saigon Sizzling Summer ad in AAA Motorist, August 1997 (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - Miss Saigon Sizzling Summer coverage in Trust News, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - Miss Saigon slide captions, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 7)
    - Miss Saigon storefronts, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 8)
    - Miss Saigon tear sheets, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 9)
    - Miss Saigon ticket information, September 1997 (Box 316, Folder 10)
    - Miss Saigon ticket reports, 1996-1997 (Box 316, Folder 11)
    - Miss Saigon ticket requests, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 12)
    - Miss Saigon ticket sales, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 13-14)
    - Miss Saigon Top of the Triangle, August 1997 (Box 316, Folder 15)
    - Miss Saigon total expenses, August 1997 (Box 316, Folder 16)
    - Miss Saigon trade tickets, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 17)
    - Miss Saigon Vietnam contacts, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 18)
    - Miss Saigon Wasser office visit, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 19)
    - Miss Saigon Westin William Penn summer package, 1997 (Box 316, Folder 20)
    - Miss Saigon windows, July 1997 (Box 316, Folder 21)
    - Tomas Kubinek, September 1997 (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - Tomas Kubinek budget, 1997 (Box 317, Folder 2)
    - Tomas Kubinek contracts, 1997 (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - Tomas Kubinek expenses, 1997 (Box 317, Folder 4)
    - Tomas Kubinek insertions, 1997 (Box 317, Folder 5)
    - Tomas Kubinek posters and advertising, October 1997 (Box 317, Folder 6)
    - Tomas Kubinek press packet, 1997 (Box 317, Folder 7)
    - Tomas Kubinek study guide, 1997 (Box 317, Folder 8)
    - Tomas Kubinek tear sheets, 1997 (Box 317, Folder 9)
    - the King and I, 1997 (Box 318, Folder 1-2)
    - the King and I advertisement confirmations, September 1997 (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - the King and I advertising, 1997 (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - the King and I gross potential, 1997 (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - the King and I market survey, 1997 (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - the King and I marketing, 1997 (Box 318, Folder 7)
    - the King and I marketing materials (Box 318, Folder 8)
    - the King and I press packet, 1997 (Box 318, Folder 9)
    - the King and I promotions, 1997 (Box 318, Folder 10)
    - the King and I sales, 1997 (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - the King and I settlement, 1997 (Box 319, Folder 2-4)
    - the King and I trades, 1997 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - the King and I WQED contract, 1997 (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - Master Class, 1997 (Box 319, Folder 7-10)
    - Master Class advertising, 1997 (Box 319, Folder 11)
    - Master Class budget, 1997 (Box 319, Folder 12)
    - Master Class business committee, November 1997 (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - Master Class contracts, 1997 (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - Master Class expenses, 1997 (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - Master Class insertions, 1997 (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - Master Class press packet and study guide, 1997 (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - Master Class sales, 1997 (Box 320, Folder 6)
    - Master Class settlement, 1997-1998 (Box 320, Folder 7)
    - Master Class trades, October 1997 (Box 320, Folder 8)
    - Moscow Boys Choir, 1997 (Box 320, Folder 9-11)
    - Moscow Boys Choir advertising, 1997 (Box 320, Folder 12)
    - Moscow Boys Choir insertions, October 1997 (Box 320, Folder 13)
    - Jim Brickman, 1997 (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - Big, 1996-1997 (Box 321, Folder 2-3)
    - Big advertisements and promotions, 1997 (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - Big advertisement samples, 1997 (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - Big contracts, 1997 (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - Big expenses, 1997 (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - Big gross potential, 1997 (Box 321, Folder 8)
    - Big insertions, 1997 (Box 321, Folder 9)
    - Big press packets, 1997 (Box 321, Folder 10)
    - Big promotions and trade agreements, 1997 (Box 321, Folder 11)
    - Big sales, 1997 (Box 321, Folder 12)
    - Big settlement, 1997-1998 (Box 321, Folder 13-15)
    - Chicago, 1997-1998 (Box 322, Folder 1-4)
    - Chicago ad proposals, 1997-1998 (Box 322, Folder 5)
    - Chicago advertising, 1997-1998 (Box 322, Folder 6)
    - Chicago contracts, 1997-1998 (Box 322, Folder 7)
    - Chicago expenses, 1997-1998 (Box 322, Folder 8)
    - Chicago expenses, 1997-1998 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - Chicago gross potential, 1997 (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - Chicago insertions, 1997 (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Chicago marketing handbook (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Chicago press packet (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Chicago sales, November 1997 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - Chicago settlement, 1997-1998 (Box 323, Folder 7-8)
    - Tap Dogs, 1997-1998 (Box 323, Folder 9-10)
    - Tap Dogs advertising, 1997 (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Tap Dogs budget, 1997-1998 (Box 324, Folder 2-3)
    - Tap Dogs contracts, 1997-1998 (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Tap Dogs insertion orders, 1997 (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Tap Dogs marketing, 1997-1998 (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Tap Dogs marketing and advertising, 1997-1998 (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - B.B. King, 1997-1998 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - My Children! My Africa!, 1995-1998 (Box 325, Folder 6-9)
    - My Children! My Africa! expenses, 1997-1998 (Box 325, Folder 10)
    - My Children! My Africa! insertions, 1998 (Box 325, Folder 11)
    - Julius Caesar, 1997-1998 (Box 325, Folder 12-14)
    - Julius Caesar expenses, 1998 (Box 325, Folder 15)
    - Julius Caesar insertions, 1998 (Box 325, Folder 16)
    - Lorie Line, 1997-1998 (Box 326, Folder 1)
    - les Miserables, 1997-1998 (Box 326, Folder 2)
    - les Miserables ad slicks, 1996-1998 (Box 326, Folder 3)
    - les Miserables advertisements and news releases,1997-1998 (Box 326, Folder 4)
    - les Miserables advertising and break evens, 1997-1998 (Box 326, Folder 5)
    - les Miserables advertising proposals and sales, 1998 (Box 326, Folder 6)
    - les Miserables budget, 1998 (Box 326, Folder 7)
    - les Miserables contracts, 1997-1998 (Box 326, Folder 8)
    - les Miserables expenses, 1998 (Box 326, Folder 9)
    - les Miserables gross potential and break evens, 1997 (Box 326, Folder 10)
    - les Miserables insertions, 1997-1998 (Box 326, Folder 11)
    - les Miserables marketing, 1997-1998 (Box 327, Folder 1)
    - les Miserables promotions, 1997-1998 (Box 327, Folder 2)
    - les Miserables tenth anniversary promotion, 1997 (Box 327, Folder 3)
    - Rent, 1997-1998 (Box 327, Folder 4-5)
    - Rent advertisements, 1997-1998 (Box 327, Folder 6)
    - Rent advertising, 1998 (Box 327, Folder 7)
    - Rent advisories, 1997 (Box 328, Folder 1)
    - Rent audition insertions, April 1998 (Box 328, Folder 2)
    - Rent budget (Box 328, Folder 3)
    - Rent contracts, 1998 (Box 328, Folder 4-5)
    - Rent expenses, 1998 (Box 328, Folder 6-7)
    - Rent gross potential and break evens, 1997 (Box 328, Folder 8)
    - Rent insertions, 1998 (Box 328, Folder 9)
    - Rent press and newspaper clippings, 1996-1998 (Box 328, Folder 10)
    - Rent press packet, 1996-1998 (Box 329, Folder 1-2)
    - Rent promotion (Box 329, Folder 3)
    - Rent sales, 1998 (Box 329, Folder 4)
    - Rent settlement, 1997-1998 (Box 329, Folder 5)
    - Rent style guide, 1997-1998 (Box 329, Folder 6)
    - Virsky's Ukrainian National Dance Company, 1998 (Box 329, Folder 7)
    - Showboat, 1997-1998 (Box 330, Folder 1-4)
    - Showboat advance sales offers, 1998 (Box 330, Folder 5)
    - Showboat advertising, 1998 (Box 330, Folder 6)
    - Showboat educational program, June 1998 (Box 331, Folder 1)
    - Showboat gala evening, 1998 (Box 331, Folder 2)
    - Showboat gross potential, 1997-1998 (Box 331, Folder 3)
    - Showboat group sales, 1998 (Box 331, Folder 4)
    - Showboat marketing, 1997-1998 (Box 331, Folder 5-6)
    - Showboat marketing, 1998 (Box 332, Folder 1)
    - Showboat North American tour binder, 1997-1998 (Box 332, Folder 2-3)
    - Showboat newspaper articles about race issue, 1997-1998 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    - Showboat on sale with 3WS, 1998 (Box 332, Folder 5)
    - Showboat promotions, 1998 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    - Showboat promotions, 1998 (Box 333, Folder 1)
    - Showboat ticket sales, June 1998 (Box 333, Folder 2)
    - Circo Zoppe' Europa, 1998 (Box 333, Folder 3)
    - Victor Victoria, 1998 (Box 333, Folder 4)
    - Victor Victoria advertising, 1998 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - Victor Victoria press packet, 1998 (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - Victor Victoria promotions, 1998 (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - Victor Victoria ticket sales, 1998 (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Tales of a Fourth Grade Nothing, 1998 (Box 333, Folder 9)
    - Tales of a Fourth Grade Nothing, 1998 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Tales of a Fourth Grade Nothing program materials, 1998 (Box 334, Folder 2)
    - Sunset Boulevard, 1998 (Box 334, Folder 3-4)
    - Sunset Boulevard advertising, 1998 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Sunset Boulevard press packet, 1998 (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - Cirque Ingenieux, 1998 (Box 334, Folder 7-8)
    - Bring in 'da Noise Bring in 'da Funk, 1998 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - Awadagin Pratt, 1996-1999 (Box 334, Folder 10-12)
    - Awadagin Pratt newspaper clippings, January 1999 (Box 334, Folder 13)
    - Awadagin Pratt press release, January 1999 (Box 334, Folder 14)
    - Awadagin Pratt program materials, January 1999 (Box 334, Folder 15)
    - Footloose, 1998-1999 (Box 334, Folder 16)
    - Footloose advisories, 1998 (Box 334, Folder 17)
    - Footloose Monroeville Mall event, 1998-1999 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Footloose Monroeville Mall event dance groups, 1998 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Footloose Monroeville Mall event information, 1999 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Rugrats, 1998-1999 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - the Gin Game, 1997-1998 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - the Gin Game advisories, 1998-1999 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Chicago, 1998-1999 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Chicago postcards, 1998 (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Chicago saving coupons, 1998-1999 (Box 335, Folder 9)
    - the Tale of Teeka, 1998-1999 (Box 335, Folder 10-11)
    - the Tale of Teeka newspaper clippings, 1999 (Box 335, Folder 12)
    - the Tale of Teeka photographs and slides, 1991 (Box 335, Folder 13)
    - the Tale of Teeka press materials, 1998-1999 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - the Tale of Teeka press release, February 1999 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - the Tale of Teeka program materials, 1999 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - Riverdance, 1998-1999 (Box 336, Folder 4-7)
    - Riverdance advisories, 1998 (Box 336, Folder 8)
    - Riverdance press packet, 1997-1998 (Box 336, Folder 9)
    - Cats, 1998-1999 (Box 336, Folder 10)
    - Cats advisories, 1998 (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - Phantom of the Opera, 1998-1999 (Box 337, Folder 1-7)
    - Phantom of the Opera advertising, 1999 (Box 337, Folder 8-9)
    - Phantom of the Opera advisories, 1998 (Box 337, Folder 10)
    - Phantom of the Opera agreement, 1994-1998 (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - Phantom of the Opera discount offers, 1999 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Phantom of the Opera group offers, 1999 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Phantom of the Opera promotions, 1999 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Phantom of the Opera settlement, 1995-1999 (Box 338, Folder 4-5)
- Audio Visual Materials, 2020-2021; IX.
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes recordings of the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust's JazzLive programs from 2020 and 2021.
  As of 2022, all of the media in this series is avaialble publicly via the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust's Youtube channel.
  - JazzLive @Home, 2020-2021; 1.
    JazzLive is the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust's jazz concert series that began in 2004. The concerts take place at various venues in the Cultural District located in downtown Pittsburgh. In 2020 and 2021, JazzLive was temporarily converted into a series of recorded interviews with jazz artists and renamed JazzLive @Home.
    - Episode 1 - Sean Jones, 2020
    - Episode 2 - Kenia, 2020
    - Episode 3 - Thomas Wendt, 2020
    - Episode 4 - Dr. Alton Merrell, 2020
    - Episode 5 - David Throckmorton, 2021
    - Episode 6 - Theron Brown, 2021
    - Episode 7 - Lynn Speakman, 2021
    - Episode 8 - Kevin Howard, 2021
    - Episode 9 - Roger Humphries + RH Factor, 2021